ejazah.com 2017-08-20

# Ejazah.com - Privacy Policy

**1\. General Principles**

i. The terms of this privacy policy (“ **Privacy Policy** ”), along with the terms of use located at [ejazah.com/Page/terms-and-conditions,](https://www.ejazah.com/Page/terms-and-conditions) constitute a legal and binding contract between you and Fursan Travel and Tourism Company Limited, a limited liability company validly existing under the laws of Kingdom of Saudi Arabia (“ **KSA** ”) (the “ **Company** ”) providing, inter alia, the terms that govern your access to use (i) the Company's website www.ejazah.com (" **Website** "), (ii) the Company's mobile and tablet applications (" **Mobile Applications** "), (iii) the Company’s online travel, ticketing, hotel reservations, vacation packages, car rentals, VIP services, visa services, customized tour packages, and allied reservation services, and (iv) any other service that may be provided by the Company from time to time (collectively referred to as the " **Services** ").It is clarified that the Company only facilitates the travel, hotel and other reservations through the use of its Services and the actual travel, accommodation, vacation, visa, or other service is rendered by a third party service provider.

ii. The Company will take reasonable care to protect your rights of privacy on systems and websites controlled by us, but the Company will not be liable for any unauthorized or unlawful disclosures of your personal and confidential information made by third parties who are not subject to the Company’s control, including but not limited to, advertisers and websites that have links to the Website. You should take note that the information and privacy policies of the Company’s business partners, advertisers, sponsors or other websites to which hyperlinks are provided, may be different from the Company’s.

iii. The Company cannot warrant the security of the information, which you transmit to us.

iv. The Company categorizes information about you (collectively referred to as " **Personal Information** ") including but not limited to, the following:

a. Profiling Information: Information which you provide when you subscribe or register for a Service:

  * Information about your personal identity such as race, gender, marital status, religion, age etc.;
  * Your financial information such as your banking details and any information relating to your income and lifestyle;
  * Your travel preferences such as meal, seat or other travel related information;
  * Your contact details such as your physical addresses, postal addresses, telephone and fax numbers; and
  * For the purpose of registering on the Company's website and Mobile Application and for Services of the Company, you hereby acknowledge and agree to undergo a mobile number verification process. The Company uses third party services for the purpose of aforesaid mobile number verification process and you hereby acknowledge, agree and confirm to be bound by the terms and conditions of such third-party service provider as applicable.

b. Service Usage: Information about your navigation using the Services, for example the URLs of websites, which you visit and from which you request downloads.

c. Log information: Information such as your web request, IP address, browser type, device type, browser language, date and time of request.

d. Transactional Information: Transactional history (other than banking details) about your e-commerce activities.

e. Correspondence Information: Content, information about your correspondents, and the destination/origin of communications between you and any other person using the Services, including but not limited to, email communications, blog, chat room and discussion board communications, instant message communications, expert forum communications, fax mail communications, membership of mailing lists.

f. User IDs: Your usernames, passwords, email addresses and other security-related information used by you in relation to our Services.

g. Stored Information: Data either created by you or by a third party and which you wish to store on the Company’s servers such as image files, documents etc.

v. The Company collects your Personal Information to conduct business and to improve and deliver the Services.

vi. The Company will only disclose your Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If the Company wants to use it for any other purpose, your consent must be obtained.

vii. In the event, you decline to submit personal information, the Company will be unable to provide the Services to you.

viii. Any information which you provide when using the Services in an unencrypted manner and/or to an open, public portal or forum including but not limited to, any blog, chat room, albums, community, classifieds, or discussion board, is not confidential, does not constitute Personal Information, and is not subject to protection under this Privacy Policy. Since such public portals are accessible by third parties, it is possible that third parties may collect, collate and use such information for their own purposes. You should accordingly be careful when deciding to share any of your Personal Information in such public portals.

ix. Information disclosed publicly, is also shared with the Company’s affiliates, third party service providers, sponsors of competitions etc., unless expressly stated otherwise.

x. The Company will not be liable to you or any third party for any damages that you or any third party may suffer howsoever arising from your disclosure of Personal Information in any public portal. You accordingly disclose information at your own risk.

xi. If you are no longer interested in receiving e-mail announcements and other marketing information from the Company, or want to remove any PII that has been collected about you, email the Company at [legal@ejazah.com](mailto:legal@ejazah.com) to notify the Company of your issue or visit [ ejazah.com/Page/privacy-policy](http://www.ejazah.com/Page/privacy-policy) _._

xii. The Company uses third-party service providers to serve ads on our behalf across the Internet and sometimes on this Website. They may collect anonymous information about your visits to the Website, and your interaction with the Services. They may also use information about your visits to this and other websites to target advertisements for goods and services. This anonymous information is collected using industry standard technology used by most major websites.

**2\. Right to collect**

i. By accepting the Company’s terms of use and Privacy Policy you agree that the Company may collect and store your Personal Information for the period you subscribe to and/or use the Services, subject to the limitations set out in this Privacy Policy.

ii. The Company collects your profiling and account information for the following reasons:

a. The Company requires your identity details, contact details, banking information and account history to manage the Company’s relationship with you and provide Services to you. The Company will only disclose this information as provided for in Clause 4 below.

b. The Company will use certain aspects of your information in an aggregated form to compile statistical and demographical profiles for business and marketing activities. The Company may disclose such information about you, provided that the information is in an aggregated form that is not capable of being used or interpreted in such a manner as to identify you.

iii. The Company collects and stores your service usage and transactional information to:

c. determine and verify the Service Charges payable by you and to administer your relationship with the Company;

d. comply with any statutory or regulatory requirement;

e. compile statistical and demographical profiles about you for business and marketing activities and to customize the Services to you. While the Company is entitled to use such information about you for internal business purposes without limitation, the Company will only disclose it in a non-aggregated form which is not capable of being used or interpreted in such a manner as to identify you; and

f. monitor your use of the Services for the purpose of ensuring compliance with the Website’s User Rules.

iv. The Company collects and stores your correspondence information and personal identifiers to:

g. comply with the Company’s obligations under Clause 4 below; and

h. monitor your use of the Services in order to ensure compliance with the Company’s User Rules as provided for in Clause 4 below.

v. The Company will only disclose correspondence information and personal identifiers under Clause 4 below.

vi. The Company may scan your Stored Information to ensure that you comply with Clause 4 below.

vii. Any Personal Information which is collected and which may be used in an aggregated format is the Company’s property. The Company may use it, in our sole discretion and without any compensation to you, for any legitimate purpose including but not limited to, the commercial sale thereof to third parties.

viii. The Company uses "cookies" to provide you with customized information when you return to the Website. "Cookies" are used to store user preferences and to track user trends, to enhance your interactive experience and generally improve the Services provided to you. You can set your browser to notify you when you are sent a "cookie", giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. If you do accept a "cookie", you thereby agree to the Company’s use of any Personal Information collected by the use of that cookie.

ix. You may update your Profiling Information at any time by using the personalize function.

x. You acknowledge and agree that in the interests of improving personalization and Service efficiency, the Company may, under controlled and secure circumstances, share your Personal Information with the Company’s affiliates (an entity which is a subsidiary or holding company or a subsidiary of the Company’s holding company or an entity which controls or is controlled by the Company).

**3\. Use of Mobile Applications**

i. When using the Company’s Mobile Applications, the Company collects and uses information about you in the same way and for the same purposes as when you use the Website.

ii. In addition to this, the Company also uses some other information that is collected automatically when you use our Mobile Apps. Specifically:

a. The Company collects information about Mobile App functionality that you access and use. This allows the Company to identify those areas of the Mobile Applications that are of interest to customers so that the Company may refine and continuously improve the Mobile Application. The information collected for this purpose does not enable the Company to directly identify you.

b. Each Mobile Application also sends us the device's unique device identifier (or "UID"), a sequence of numbers or characters that are unique to your mobile device. The Company uses this only on the first opening of the Mobile Application so that we can confirm to advertising networks the number of downloads resulting from clicks on their respective advertisement banners and other marketing tools.

c. When you use a Mobile Applications, you may choose to allow access to your current location – provided by your mobile device using GPS or similar technologies – in order to identify nearby hotels or airports. If you choose to allow access, this location data may be collected anonymously as part of search requests logged by the Company’s servers. You may switch off the Mobile Application’s access to your location at any time through your mobile device’s settings menu.

d. The Mobile Application may also sync with the calendar on your mobile devices, which enables the Company to put your travel itinerary on your individual calendar.

e. Each Mobile Application will also send the Company error-reporting information in the event that it crashes or hangs. This enables the Company to investigate the error and to improve the stability of the Mobile Application for future releases. As part of these error reports, the Mobile Application sends us information about the mobile device type and version, the UID, the time the error occurred, the feature being used and the state of the application when the error occurred. The Company does not use this information for any purpose other than investigating and remedying the error.

iii. You have the ability to control what information a Mobile Application sends to the Company. You may exercise this control either by changing the settings of the Mobile Application under its settings menu or changing the settings of your mobile device. Alternatively, you may remove the Mobile Application from your mobile device entirely and the Services through the Website.

**4\. Cookies**

iv. The use of cookies is essential to you, to facilitate navigation of the Website, for statistical purposes as well as provide business and marketing information to the Company. The information the Company collects and analyzes is used to improve the Services provided on this Website to you.

v. You expressly consent to use of cookies and for the Website’s cookies policy in accordance with the cookies notification that appears when accessing the Website, except in the case that they have modified the browser settings to block them. You are encouraged to use the “clear cookies” functionality of your browsers to ensure deletion, as the Company cannot guarantee, predict or provide for the behavior of the equipment of all users of the Website.

vi. The Company uses cookies to provide you with customized information when you return to the Website. Cookies are used to store user preferences and to track user trends, to enhance your interactive experience

**5\. General exceptions**

i. If the Company is required to intercept, disclose, monitor and/or store your Personal Information:

a. by law;

b. to conduct the Company’s business;

c. to secure the Company’s systems; or

d. to enforce the Company’s own rights, which will be done in the manner as prescribed by legislation.

ii. Such interception, disclosure, monitoring and storage may take place without your knowledge. In that case, the Company will not be liable to you or any third party for any damages howsoever arising from such interception, disclosure, monitoring and storage.

iii. In order to ensure that you comply with the User Rules, the Company may monitor your Personal Information to the extent that this may be required to determine compliance and/or to identify instances of non-compliance.

iv. To ensure that the security and integrity of the Services are safeguarded, the Company may monitor your Personal Information. This monitoring may include (without limitation) the filtering of incoming and outgoing electronic data messages to identify, limit and/or prevent the transmission of spam, viruses and/or unlawful, defamatory, obscene or otherwise undesirable material or content.

v. The Company may under certain circumstances procure an element of the Services from a third-party service provider for example the Company may use third-party advertising companies to serve advertisements when you visit the Website. To the extent that it may be necessary, and solely for the purposes of providing Services to you, you agree that the Company may disclose to such third-party any of your Personal Information that may be necessary for the procurement of services from the third-party. These companies may also use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. More information about this practice and your choices about not having this information used by these companies would be available with the respective third-parties.

vi. In addition to the general limitation found in the Terms of Use on the Website, the Company will not be liable to you or any other third party for any damages (as defined in Clause 14 of the Terms of Use, found on the Website) suffered by you or any other third party howsoever arising from the disclosure of your Personal Information. Your only remedy under such circumstances will be to end this agreement.

**6\. User Requirements**

vii. You are required to provide accurate and updated Personal Information in order to establish and manage your contractual relationship with the Company and duly reserve and purchase the selected Services. You acknowledge that by providing inaccurate personal data you are restricting the Company and third-parties from successfully providing its services.

viii. You will be liable for any misappropriation of Personal Information, including but not limited to, fraud and identity theft and the Company is indemnified from any such instances of misappropriation

**7\. External Links**

If any part of the Website links you to other websites, those websites do not operate under this Privacy Policy. The Company recommends you examine the privacy statements posted on those other websites to understand their procedures for collecting, using, and disclosing personal information.

**8\. Children’s Policy**

The Company does not provide Services on the Website and/or Mobile Apps for purchase by children. If you are under the age of 18 and this information is provided to the Company, the Services being availed by you will be immediately aborted and the transaction will not be processed, at the sole discretion of the Company. Purchase of Services to be rendered by the Company will only be successful when obtained by a person of or over the age of 18. You will be held personally liable and you shall indemnify the Company for any claims and liabilities arising out of or in connection with any such false information provided by you on the Website or Mobile Apps, including but not limited to your age.

**9\. Changes to this Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy may be amended regularly to ensure ongoing compliance with all relevant regulations in the event of amendment or revision. You shall take sole responsibility of regularly accessing the Company’s Privacy

Policy to ensure you are updated and aware of the Privacy Policies. If you are a registered user of the Website and/or Mobile Apps, you will receive notification of any upcoming amendments or updates to the Privacy Policy.

**10\. Contact Information**

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy or any other queries relates to the Services provided, please contact us at the information below:

Fursan Travel and Tourism LLC Legal department

King Fahad Road, Olaya Riyadh 11594

Kingdom of Saudi Arabia

Telephone +966 11 239 1160 Email [ legal@](mailto:legal@ejazah.com)[ejazah.com](mailto:legal@ejazah.com)
